Jibran Shoukat

+92 313 5113986 \cdot abduljibran62@gmail.com \cdot Pakistan

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Ambitious real estate agent and content creator with over 4 years of diverse experience across local, corporate, and online platforms. Specialties include exceptional communication and interpersonal skills, creative idea generation, graphic design, video production, customer service, content strategy, scriptwriting, and comprehensive content creation. Excited to leverage my expertise to contribute to the growth of your organization.

SKILLS

Customer service **Content Creator** Video Editing Creative Negotiation Hosting/ Presenter Video Production Team work Proactive and self-motivated Strong interpersonal skills **Graphic Designing** Acting Real Estate knowledge Scriptwriting **Adobe Creative Suite** Exceptional organizational skills Networking Storytelling MS Office **Problem Solving**

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance Apr 2021- Present

Real Estate Agent & Content Creator

As a freelance real estate agent, I managed sales and property content creation, including editing videos, generating content ideas, creating digital ads, scriptwriting, and videography. It enhanced my interpersonal skills, communication abilities, and video production proficiency, ultimately resulting in significant growth.

Liaqat and Co (Pvt Ltd)

Media Head & Real Estate Agent

As a real estate agent, I handled sales and purchases, created engaging content, and made promotional videos, and that leading to a doubling of sales, then I received appreciation for my outstanding performance and being a real estate agent sharpened my skills in creativity, public dealing, communication, and sales techniques.

Hot Grill Catering Jul 2017 - Sep 2019

Operations Manager

I managed food quality and stock levels, led and coordinated the team, ensured hygiene and taste standards, and focused on satisfying clients.

| Telemarketing March 2016- May 2017

Customer Service Representative

I provided detailed product information, promptly addressed customer queries, and resolved issues professionally. I also collaborated internally for seamless communication, updating product knowledge to enhance services.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Media Studies, 2024

Iqra University, Islamabad

HSSC (Pre-Engineering), 2016

Steps College, Rawalpindi

English Langauge Course, 2016

Leadership College, Rawalpindi

SSC (Computer Science), 2014

Govt Comprehensive High School, Rawalpindi

PROJECTS & ACTIVITIES

Sales and Marketing

Successfully closed 17 deals in a month

Video Production

Doubled the sales and purchases through content

Mar 2020 - Apr 2021

Volunteering, Charity Campaigns

Rwp, Islamabad [Wall of Kind, Raashan]

Social Media Manager

Successfully ran promotional campaigns

ACHIEVEMENTS AND CERTIFICATES

Best CSR: J Telemarketing

Remarkable Performance: Hot Grill Catering

Best Actor (Theatre): Igra University

Media Head Appreciation: Liaqat and Co

Excellent Performance Appreciation: Makaan Solutions

LANGUAGE

English Urdu Pahari Punjabi